{"ModDate": "D:20001219094341+08'00'", "CreationDate": "D:19990924131032", "Producer": "Acrobat 3.0 Import Plug-in\u0000", "Creator": "Acrobat 3.0 Import Plug-in\u0000", "content": "RRP: THA 26227\n\n          ASIAN DEVELOPMENT BANK \n\nREPORT AND RECOMMENDATION \n \nOF THE \n \nPRESIDENT \n \nTO THE \n \nBOARD OF DIRECTORS \n \nON A \n \nPROPOSED LOAN \n \nTO THE \n \nKINGDOM OF THAILAND \n \nFOR THE \n \nSAMUT PRAKARN WASTEWATER MANAGEMENT PROJECT \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \nNovember 1995 \n\n \n \n \n\n \n\n \n\n\fCURRENCY EQUIVALENTS \n(as of 31 October 1995) \n \n\nCurrency Unit  \n\n \n\nB 1.00   \n \n$ 1.00 \n\n \n\n \n \n\n \n\n \n \n\nBaht (B) \n\n$0.039984 \nB25.01 \n\nFor the calculations in this Report an exchange rate of B25.00 = $1.00  \nhas been used. This was the rate prevailing at the time of appraisal \n \nABBREVIATIONS \n\n \n\n \n\nBangkok Metropolitan Administration \nBenefit Monitoring and Evaluation \nBangkok Metropolitan Region \nBiochemical Oxygen Demand \nBuild Operate and Transfer \nDanish Cooperation for Environment and Development \nDissolved Oxygen \nEnvironmental Impact Assessment \nEconomic Internal Rate of Return \nInternational Competitive Bidding \nInitial Environmental Examination \nIndustrial Pollution Prevention and Clean Technology \n \nMinistry of Science, Technology and Environment \nMetropolitan Waterworks Authority \nNational Environmental Quality Act \nNongovernment Organization \nOverseas Economic Cooperation Fund – Japan \nOperation and Maintenance \nPollution Control Department \nProvincial Waterworks Authority \nSamut Prakam Water Pollution Control Unit \nTechnical Assistance \nWastewater Management Authority \n\nTransfer \n\n \n \n\n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n\n \n\n \n \n\n \n \n \n \n \n\n \n \n \n \n \n\nBMA \nBME \nBMR \nBOD \nBOT \nDANCED \n \nDO \n \nEIA \n \nEIRR \n \nICB \nIEE \n \nIPP-CTT \n \n \nMOSTE  \nMWA \n \nNEQA   \nNGO \n \nOECF   \n \nO&M \n \nPCD \nPWA \n \nSPWPCU \nTA \nWMA \n \n\n \n \n\n \n\n \n \n\n \n \n \n \n \n \n\n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n\n \n \n \n \n \n\nha \nkm \nkm2 \nm3/d \nmg/l \n\nWEIGHTS AND MEASURE \n \nhectare \nkilometer \nsquare kilometers \ncubic meters per day \nmilligram per liter \n\n \n \n \n \n \n\n \n \n \n \n \n\n(i) \n(ii) \n\nThe fiscal year of the Government ends on 30 September \nIn this Report, “$” refers to US dollars. \n\nNOTES \n \n\n \n\n \n\n \n \n \n \n \n\n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n\n \n\n\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f\f", "author_pages": ["CURRENCY EQUIVALENTS \n(as of 31 October 1995) \n \n", "Currency Unit  \n", " \n", "B 1.00   \n \n$ 1.00 \n", " \n", " \n \n", " \n", " \n \n", "Baht (B) \n", "$0.039984 \nB25.01 \n", "For the calculations in this Report an exchange rate of B25.00 = $1.00  \nhas been used. This was the rate prevailing at the time of appraisal \n \nABBREVIATIONS \n", " \n", " \n", "Bangkok Metropolitan Administration \nBenefit Monitoring and Evaluation \nBangkok Metropolitan Region \nBiochemical Oxygen Demand \nBuild Operate and Transfer \nDanish Cooperation for Environment and Development \nDissolved Oxygen \nEnvironmental Impact Assessment \nEconomic Internal Rate of Return \nInternational Competitive Bidding \nInitial Environmental Examination \nIndustrial Pollution Prevention and Clean Technology \n \nMinistry of Science, Technology and Environment \nMetropolitan Waterworks Authority \nNational Environmental Quality Act \nNongovernment Organization \nOverseas Economic Cooperation Fund – Japan \nOperation and Maintenance \nPollution Control Department \nProvincial Waterworks Authority \nSamut Prakam Water Pollution Control Unit \nTechnical Assistance \nWastewater Management Authority \n", "Transfer \n", " \n \n", " \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n", " \n", " \n \n", " \n \n \n \n \n", " \n \n \n \n \n", "BMA \nBME \nBMR \nBOD \nBOT \nDANCED \n \nDO \n \nEIA \n \nEIRR \n \nICB \nIEE \n \nIPP-CTT \n \n \nMOSTE  \nMWA \n \nNEQA   \nNGO \n \nOECF   \n \nO&M \n \nPCD \nPWA \n \nSPWPCU \nTA \nWMA \n \n", " \n \n", " \n", " \n \n", " \n \n \n \n \n \n", "= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n= \n", " \n \n \n \n \n", "ha \nkm \nkm2 \nm3/d \nmg/l \n", "WEIGHTS AND MEASURE \n \nhectare \nkilometer \nsquare kilometers \ncubic meters per day \nmilligram per liter \n", " \n \n \n \n \n", " \n \n \n \n \n", "(i) \n(ii) \n", "The fiscal year of the Government ends on 30 September \nIn this Report, “$” refers to US dollars. \n", "NOTES \n \n", " \n", " \n", " \n \n \n \n \n", " \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n \n", " \n"], "classified_text": [["RRP", "O"], [":", "O"], ["THA", "O"], ["26227", "O"], ["ASIAN", "O"], ["DEVELOPMENT", "O"], ["BANK", "O"], ["REPORT", "O"], ["AND", "O"], ["RECOMMENDATION", "O"], ["OF", "O"], ["THE", "O"], ["PRESIDENT", "O"], ["TO", "O"], ["THE", "O"], ["BOARD", "O"], ["OF", "O"], ["DIRECTORS", "O"], ["ON", "O"], ["A", "O"], ["PROPOSED", "O"], ["LOAN", "O"], ["TO", "O"], ["THE", "O"], ["KINGDOM", "O"], ["OF", "O"], ["THAILAND", "LOCATION"], ["FOR", "O"], ["THE", "O"], ["SAMUT", "O"], ["PRAKARN", "O"], ["WASTEWATER", "O"], ["MANAGEMENT", "O"], ["PROJECT", "O"], ["November", "O"], ["1995", "O"], ["CURRENCY", "O"], ["EQUIVALENTS", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["as", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["31", "O"], ["October", "O"], ["1995", "O"], [")", "O"], ["Currency", "O"], ["Unit", "O"], ["B", "O"], ["1.00", "O"], ["$", "O"], ["1.00", "O"], ["Baht", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["B", "O"], [")", "O"], ["$", "O"], ["0.039984", "O"], ["B25.01", "O"], ["For", "O"], ["the", "O"], ["calculations", "O"], ["in", "O"], ["this", "O"], ["Report", "O"], ["an", "O"], ["exchange", "O"], ["rate", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["B25.00", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["$", "O"], ["1.00", "O"], ["has", "O"], ["been", "O"], ["used", "O"], [".", "O"], ["This", "O"], ["was", "O"], ["the", "O"], ["rate", "O"], ["prevailing", "O"], ["at", "O"], ["the", "O"], ["time", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["appraisal", "O"], ["ABBREVIATIONS", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Bangkok", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Metropolitan", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Administration", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Benefit", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Monitoring", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "O"], ["Evaluation", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Bangkok", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Metropolitan", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Region", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Biochemical", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Oxygen", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Demand", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Build", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Operate", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Transfer", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Danish", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Cooperation", "ORGANIZATION"], ["for", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environment", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Development", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Dissolved", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Oxygen", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environmental", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Impact", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Assessment", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Economic", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Internal", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Rate", "ORGANIZATION"], ["of", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Return", "ORGANIZATION"], ["International", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Competitive", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Bidding", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Initial", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environmental", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Examination", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Industrial", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Pollution", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Prevention", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Clean", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Technology", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Ministry", "ORGANIZATION"], ["of", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Science", "ORGANIZATION"], [",", "O"], ["Technology", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environment", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Metropolitan", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Waterworks", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Authority", "ORGANIZATION"], ["National", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environmental", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Quality", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Act", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Nongovernment", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Organization", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Overseas", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Economic", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Cooperation", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Fund", "ORGANIZATION"], ["–", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Japan", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Operation", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Maintenance", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Pollution", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Control", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Department", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Provincial", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Waterworks", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Authority", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Samut", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Prakam", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Water", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Pollution", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Control", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Unit", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Technical", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Assistance", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Wastewater", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Management", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Authority", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Transfer", "ORGANIZATION"], ["BMA", "ORGANIZATION"], ["BME", "O"], ["BMR", "O"], ["BOD", "O"], ["BOT", "O"], ["DANCED", "O"], ["DO", "O"], ["EIA", "O"], ["EIRR", "O"], ["ICB", "O"], ["IEE", "O"], ["IPP-CTT", "O"], ["MOSTE", "O"], ["MWA", "O"], ["NEQA", "O"], ["NGO", "O"], ["OECF", "O"], ["O", "O"], ["&", "O"], ["M", "O"], ["PCD", "O"], ["PWA", "O"], ["SPWPCU", "O"], ["TA", "O"], ["WMA", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["ha", "O"], ["km", "O"], ["km2", "O"], ["m3d", "O"], ["mgl", "O"], ["WEIGHTS", "O"], ["AND", "O"], ["MEASURE", "O"], ["hectare", "O"], ["kilometer", "O"], ["square", "O"], ["kilometers", "O"], ["cubic", "O"], ["meters", "O"], ["per", "O"], ["day", "O"], ["milligram", "O"], ["per", "O"], ["liter", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["i", "O"], [")", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["ii", "O"], [")", "O"], ["The", "O"], ["fiscal", "O"], ["year", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["the", "O"], ["Government", "O"], ["ends", "O"], ["on", "O"], ["30", "O"], ["September", "O"], ["In", "O"], ["this", "O"], ["Report", "O"], [",", "O"], ["“", "O"], ["$", "O"], ["”", "O"], ["refers", "O"], ["to", "O"], ["US", "O"], ["dollars", "O"], [".", "O"], ["NOTES", "O"]], "classified_author_pages": [["CURRENCY", "O"], ["EQUIVALENTS", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["as", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["31", "O"], ["October", "O"], ["1995", "O"], [")", "O"], ["Currency", "O"], ["Unit", "O"], ["B", "O"], ["1.00", "O"], ["$", "O"], ["1.00", "O"], ["Baht", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["B", "O"], [")", "O"], ["$", "O"], ["0.039984", "O"], ["B25.01", "O"], ["For", "O"], ["the", "O"], ["calculations", "O"], ["in", "O"], ["this", "O"], ["Report", "O"], ["an", "O"], ["exchange", "O"], ["rate", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["B25.00", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["$", "O"], ["1.00", "O"], ["has", "O"], ["been", "O"], ["used", "O"], [".", "O"], ["This", "O"], ["was", "O"], ["the", "O"], ["rate", "O"], ["prevailing", "O"], ["at", "O"], ["the", "O"], ["time", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["appraisal", "O"], ["ABBREVIATIONS", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Bangkok", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Metropolitan", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Administration", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Benefit", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Monitoring", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "O"], ["Evaluation", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Bangkok", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Metropolitan", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Region", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Biochemical", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Oxygen", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Demand", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Build", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Operate", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Transfer", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Danish", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Cooperation", "ORGANIZATION"], ["for", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environment", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Development", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Dissolved", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Oxygen", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environmental", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Impact", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Assessment", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Economic", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Internal", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Rate", "ORGANIZATION"], ["of", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Return", "ORGANIZATION"], ["International", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Competitive", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Bidding", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Initial", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environmental", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Examination", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Industrial", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Pollution", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Prevention", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Clean", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Technology", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Ministry", "ORGANIZATION"], ["of", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Science", "ORGANIZATION"], [",", "O"], ["Technology", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environment", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Metropolitan", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Waterworks", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Authority", "ORGANIZATION"], ["National", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Environmental", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Quality", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Act", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Nongovernment", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Organization", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Overseas", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Economic", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Cooperation", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Fund", "ORGANIZATION"], ["–", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Japan", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Operation", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Maintenance", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Pollution", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Control", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Department", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Provincial", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Waterworks", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Authority", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Samut", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Prakam", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Water", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Pollution", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Control", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Unit", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Technical", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Assistance", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Wastewater", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Management", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Authority", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Transfer", "ORGANIZATION"], ["BMA", "ORGANIZATION"], ["BME", "O"], ["BMR", "O"], ["BOD", "O"], ["BOT", "O"], ["DANCED", "O"], ["DO", "O"], ["EIA", "O"], ["EIRR", "O"], ["ICB", "O"], ["IEE", "O"], ["IPP-CTT", "O"], ["MOSTE", "O"], ["MWA", "O"], ["NEQA", "O"], ["NGO", "O"], ["OECF", "O"], ["O", "O"], ["&", "O"], ["M", "O"], ["PCD", "O"], ["PWA", "O"], ["SPWPCU", "O"], ["TA", "O"], ["WMA", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["=", "O"], ["ha", "O"], ["km", "O"], ["km2", "O"], ["m3d", "O"], ["mgl", "O"], ["WEIGHTS", "O"], ["AND", "O"], ["MEASURE", "O"], ["hectare", "O"], ["kilometer", "O"], ["square", "O"], ["kilometers", "O"], ["cubic", "O"], ["meters", "O"], ["per", "O"], ["day", "O"], ["milligram", "O"], ["per", "O"], ["liter", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["i", "O"], [")", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["ii", "O"], [")", "O"], ["The", "O"], ["fiscal", "O"], ["year", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["the", "O"], ["Government", "O"], ["ends", "O"], ["on", "O"], ["30", "O"], ["September", "O"], ["In", "O"], ["this", "O"], ["Report", "O"], [",", "O"], ["“", "O"], ["$", "O"], ["”", "O"], ["refers", "O"], ["to", "O"], ["US", "O"], ["dollars", "O"], [".", "O"], ["NOTES", "O"]]}