{"Author": "Asian Development Bank", "Company": "Asian Development Bank", "CreationDate": "D:20150213075013+08'00'", "Creator": "Acrobat PDFMaker 11 for Word", "Keywords": "\"shortlisted firms, shortlist\"", "ModDate": "D:20150213075046+08'00'", "Producer": "Adobe PDF Library 11.0", "SourceModified": "D:20150212234954", "Subject": "This document contains the shortlisted consulting firms for a specific technical assistance, grant or staff consultancy project.", "Title": "TA No. 8849-VIE: Support to Border Areas Development - 01 Preparation for Support to Border Areas Development Project (48189-001)", "content": " \n \n \n \n \n Technical Assistance – Shortlisted Consulting Firms \n \n \n \nVIET NAM, SOCIALIST REPUBLIC OF \n \n \nTA No. 8849-VIE: Support to Border Areas Development - 01 Preparation for Support to \nBorder Areas Development Project (48189-001) \n \nRFP Issuance Date: 12 February 2015 \n \n \nFirm Name  \n\n:   Joint venture between CONTRANS AB and Transport Engineering \nConsultant Joint Stock Company No.2, in association with ASEAN \nDevelopment and Management Consulting Ltd. \n\nAddress  \nPhone  \nFax  \nEmail  \nContact Person  \nDesignation  \n  \nFirm Name  \n\n:   Tallboangen 65, Askim 43644 Sweden  \n:   +46-31-283835 \n:   +46-31-284857 \n:   hans.orn@contrans.se \n:   Hans Orn \n:   President \n  \n:   Dainichi Consultant Inc., in association with South Transport \n\n  \n\nEngineering Design Joint Stock Incorporated \n\nAddress  \nPhone  \nFax  \nEmail  \nContact Person  \nDesignation  \n  \nFirm Name  \nAddress  \nPhone  \nEmail  \nContact Person  \nDesignation  \n  \nFirm Name  \n\nInternational Business Division \n  \n\n:   3-1-21 Yabuta Minami, Gifu, Japan 500-8384  \n:   81-58-271-2502 \n:   81-58-274-5325 \n:   kaigai-dci@dainichi-consul.co.jp \n:   Kaigai Dainichi \n:  \n  \n:   Egis International \n:   15, avenue du Centre, Saint-Quentin-en-Yvelines 78286 Cedex France  \n:   + 33 1 39 41 40 00 \n:   blandine.forthomme@egis.fr \n:   Gilles Pequeux \n:   Director, Business Development Department \n  \n:   Joint venture between SAI Consulting Engineers Pvt. Ltd. and \n\n  \n\nMeghraj Capital Advisors Private Limited \n“SAI House”, Satyam Corporate Square, B/H. Rajpath Club,  \nBodakdev, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380 059 India  \n\nAddress  \n \nPhone  \nFax  \nEmail  \nContact Person  \nDesignation  \n  \n\n:  \n \n:   +91-079-66142600 / 2700 \n:   +91-079-66142900 \n:   mail@saiindia.com \n:   Dhaval Parikh \n:   Executive Director & COO \n  \n\n  \n\n \n\n\f2 \n\n \n\nFirm Name  \n\n:   Joint venture between SPT - Studi E Pianificazione Del Territorio \n\n  \n\nS.R.L. and Umar Munshi Associates \n:   Via Tuscolana 336, Rome, RM 00181 Italy  \n:   +39 06 7805976 \n:   +39 06 97610727 \n:   spt@spt-roma.it \n:   Sergio Polizzotti \n:   General Manager \n  \n:   South Asia Management And Engineering Services (Sames) Pvt. Ltd \n:   Flat No- C-1 (3 rd Floor), House-11, Road-20, Sector-3, Uttara,  \n  Dhaka-1230 Bangladesh  \n:   0088-02-7912540 \n:   0088-02-7912540 / 00977-1-44-26-269 \n:   HEDAYETUL.SAMES@YAHOO.COM \n:   Hedayetul Islam \n:   CEO \n  \n  \n\nAddress  \nPhone  \nFax  \nEmail  \nContact Person  \nDesignation  \n  \nFirm Name  \nAddress  \n \nPhone  \nFax  \nEmail  \nContact Person  \nDesignation  \n  \n \nClosing date for submission of proposals is on 19 March 2015. \n \n\n\f", "author_pages": ["2 \n", " \n", "Firm Name  \n", ":   Joint venture between SPT - Studi E Pianificazione Del Territorio \n", "  \n", "S.R.L. and Umar Munshi Associates \n:   Via Tuscolana 336, Rome, RM 00181 Italy  \n:   +39 06 7805976 \n:   +39 06 97610727 \n:   spt@spt-roma.it \n:   Sergio Polizzotti \n:   General Manager \n  \n:   South Asia Management And Engineering Services (Sames) Pvt. Ltd \n:   Flat No- C-1 (3 rd Floor), House-11, Road-20, Sector-3, Uttara,  \n  Dhaka-1230 Bangladesh  \n:   0088-02-7912540 \n:   0088-02-7912540 / 00977-1-44-26-269 \n:   HEDAYETUL.SAMES@YAHOO.COM \n:   Hedayetul Islam \n:   CEO \n  \n  \n", "Address  \nPhone  \nFax  \nEmail  \nContact Person  \nDesignation  \n  \nFirm Name  \nAddress  \n \nPhone  \nFax  \nEmail  \nContact Person  \nDesignation  \n  \n \nClosing date for submission of proposals is on 19 March 2015. \n \n"], "classified_text": [["Technical", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Assistance", "ORGANIZATION"], ["–", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Shortlisted", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Consulting", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Firms", "ORGANIZATION"], ["VIET", "ORGANIZATION"], ["NAM", "ORGANIZATION"], [",", "O"], ["SOCIALIST", "O"], ["REPUBLIC", "O"], ["OF", "O"], ["TA", "O"], ["No", "O"], [".", "O"], ["8849-VIE", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Support", "O"], ["to", "O"], ["Border", "O"], ["Areas", "O"], ["Development", "O"], ["-", "O"], ["01", "O"], ["Preparation", "O"], ["for", "O"], ["Support", "O"], ["to", "O"], ["Border", "O"], ["Areas", "O"], ["Development", "O"], ["Project", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["48189-001", "O"], [")", "O"], ["RFP", "O"], ["Issuance", "O"], ["Date", "O"], [":", "O"], ["12", "O"], ["February", "O"], ["2015", "O"], ["Firm", "O"], ["Name", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Joint", "O"], ["venture", "O"], ["between", "O"], ["CONTRANS", "ORGANIZATION"], ["AB", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "O"], ["Transport", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Engineering", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Consultant", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Joint", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Stock", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Company", "ORGANIZATION"], ["No.2", "O"], [",", "O"], ["in", "O"], ["association", "O"], ["with", "O"], ["ASEAN", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Development", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Management", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Consulting", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Ltd", "ORGANIZATION"], [".", "O"], ["Address", "O"], ["Phone", "O"], ["Fax", "O"], ["Email", "O"], ["Contact", "O"], ["Person", "O"], ["Designation", "O"], ["Firm", "O"], ["Name", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Tallboangen", "ORGANIZATION"], ["65", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Askim", "PERSON"], ["43644", "O"], ["Sweden", "O"], [":", "O"], ["+46-31-283835", "O"], [":", "O"], ["+46-31-284857", "O"], [":", "O"], ["hans.orn", "O"], ["@", "O"], ["contrans.se", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Hans", "PERSON"], ["Orn", "PERSON"], [":", "O"], ["President", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Dainichi", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Consultant", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Inc.", "ORGANIZATION"], [",", "O"], ["in", "O"], ["association", "O"], ["with", "O"], ["South", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Transport", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Engineering", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Design", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Joint", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Stock", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Incorporated", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Address", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Phone", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Fax", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Email", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Contact", "O"], ["Person", "O"], ["Designation", "O"], ["Firm", "O"], ["Name", "O"], ["Address", "O"], ["Phone", "O"], ["Email", "O"], ["Contact", "O"], ["Person", "O"], ["Designation", "O"], ["Firm", "O"], ["Name", "O"], ["International", "O"], ["Business", "O"], ["Division", "O"], [":", "O"], ["3-1-21", "O"], ["Yabuta", "PERSON"], ["Minami", "PERSON"], [",", "O"], ["Gifu", "LOCATION"], [",", "O"], ["Japan", "LOCATION"], ["500-8384", "O"], [":", "O"], ["81-58-271-2502", "O"], [":", "O"], ["81-58-274-5325", "O"], [":", "O"], ["kaigai-dci", "O"], ["@", "O"], ["dainichi-consul.co.jp", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Kaigai", "O"], ["Dainichi", "O"], [":", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Egis", "O"], ["International", "O"], [":", "O"], ["15", "O"], [",", "O"], ["avenue", "O"], ["du", "O"], ["Centre", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Saint-Quentin-en-Yvelines", "LOCATION"], ["78286", "O"], ["Cedex", "O"], ["France", "O"], [":", "O"], ["+", "O"], ["33", "O"], ["1", "O"], ["39", "O"], ["41", "O"], ["40", "O"], ["00", "O"], [":", "O"], ["blandine.forthomme", "O"], ["@", "O"], ["egis.fr", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Gilles", "PERSON"], ["Pequeux", "PERSON"], [":", "O"], ["Director", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Business", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Development", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Department", "ORGANIZATION"], [":", "O"], ["Joint", "O"], ["venture", "O"], ["between", "O"], ["SAI", "O"], ["Consulting", "O"], ["Engineers", "O"], ["Pvt", "O"], [".", "O"], ["Ltd.", "ORGANIZATION"], ["and", "O"], ["Meghraj", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Capital", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Advisors", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Private", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Limited", "ORGANIZATION"], ["“", "O"], ["SAI", "O"], ["House", "O"], ["”", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Satyam", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Corporate", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Square", "ORGANIZATION"], [",", "O"], ["BH", "O"], [".", "O"], ["Rajpath", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Club", "ORGANIZATION"], [",", "O"], ["Bodakdev", "PERSON"], [",", "O"], ["Ahmedabad", "LOCATION"], [",", "O"], ["Gujarat", "LOCATION"], ["380", "O"], ["059", "O"], ["India", "LOCATION"], ["Address", "O"], ["Phone", "O"], ["Fax", "O"], ["Email", "O"], ["Contact", "O"], ["Person", "O"], ["Designation", "O"], [":", "O"], [":", "O"], ["+91-079-66142600", "O"], ["", "O"], ["2700", "O"], [":", "O"], ["+91-079-66142900", "O"], [":", "O"], ["mail", "O"], ["@", "O"], ["saiindia.com", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Dhaval", "PERSON"], ["Parikh", "PERSON"], [":", "O"], ["Executive", "O"], ["Director", "O"], ["&", "O"], ["COO", "O"], ["2", "O"], ["Firm", "O"], ["Name", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Joint", "O"], ["venture", "O"], ["between", "O"], ["SPT", "ORGANIZATION"], ["-", "O"], ["Studi", "ORGANIZATION"], ["E", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Pianificazione", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Del", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Territorio", "ORGANIZATION"], ["S.R.L", "ORGANIZATION"], [".", "O"], ["and", "O"], ["Umar", "PERSON"], ["Munshi", "PERSON"], ["Associates", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Via", "O"], ["Tuscolana", "O"], ["336", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Rome", "LOCATION"], [",", "O"], ["RM", "O"], ["00181", "O"], ["Italy", "LOCATION"], [":", "O"], ["+39", "O"], ["06", "O"], ["7805976", "O"], [":", "O"], ["+39", "O"], ["06", "O"], ["97610727", "O"], [":", "O"], ["spt", "O"], ["@", "O"], ["spt-roma.it", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Sergio", "PERSON"], ["Polizzotti", "PERSON"], [":", "O"], ["General", "O"], ["Manager", "O"], [":", "O"], ["South", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Asia", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Management", "ORGANIZATION"], ["And", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Engineering", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Services", "ORGANIZATION"], ["(", "O"], ["Sames", "O"], [")", "O"], ["Pvt", "O"], [".", "O"], ["Ltd", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Flat", "O"], ["No-", "O"], ["C-1", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["3", "O"], ["rd", "O"], ["Floor", "O"], [")", "O"], [",", "O"], ["House-11", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Road-20", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Sector-3", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Uttara", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Dhaka-1230", "O"], ["Bangladesh", "LOCATION"], [":", "O"], ["0088-02-7912540", "O"], [":", "O"], ["0088-02-7912540", "O"], ["", "O"], ["00977-1-44-26-269", "O"], [":", "O"], ["HEDAYETUL.SAMES", "O"], ["@", "O"], ["YAHOO.COM", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Hedayetul", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Islam", "ORGANIZATION"], [":", "O"], ["CEO", "O"], ["Address", "O"], ["Phone", "O"], ["Fax", "O"], ["Email", "O"], ["Contact", "O"], ["Person", "O"], ["Designation", "O"], ["Firm", "O"], ["Name", "O"], ["Address", "O"], ["Phone", "O"], ["Fax", "O"], ["Email", "O"], ["Contact", "O"], ["Person", "O"], ["Designation", "O"], ["Closing", "O"], ["date", "O"], ["for", "O"], ["submission", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["proposals", "O"], ["is", "O"], ["on", "O"], ["19", "O"], ["March", "O"], ["2015", "O"], [".", "O"]], "classified_author_pages": [["2", "O"], ["Firm", "O"], ["Name", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Joint", "O"], ["venture", "O"], ["between", "O"], ["SPT", "ORGANIZATION"], ["-", "O"], ["Studi", "ORGANIZATION"], ["E", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Pianificazione", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Del", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Territorio", "ORGANIZATION"], ["S.R.L", "ORGANIZATION"], [".", "O"], ["and", "O"], ["Umar", "PERSON"], ["Munshi", "PERSON"], ["Associates", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Via", "O"], ["Tuscolana", "O"], ["336", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Rome", "LOCATION"], [",", "O"], ["RM", "O"], ["00181", "O"], ["Italy", "LOCATION"], [":", "O"], ["+39", "O"], ["06", "O"], ["7805976", "O"], [":", "O"], ["+39", "O"], ["06", "O"], ["97610727", "O"], [":", "O"], ["spt", "O"], ["@", "O"], ["spt-roma.it", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Sergio", "PERSON"], ["Polizzotti", "PERSON"], [":", "O"], ["General", "O"], ["Manager", "O"], [":", "O"], ["South", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Asia", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Management", "ORGANIZATION"], ["And", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Engineering", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Services", "ORGANIZATION"], ["(", "O"], ["Sames", "O"], [")", "O"], ["Pvt", "O"], [".", "O"], ["Ltd", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Flat", "O"], ["No-", "O"], ["C-1", "O"], ["(", "O"], ["3", "O"], ["rd", "O"], ["Floor", "O"], [")", "O"], [",", "O"], ["House-11", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Road-20", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Sector-3", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Uttara", "O"], [",", "O"], ["Dhaka-1230", "O"], ["Bangladesh", "LOCATION"], [":", "O"], ["0088-02-7912540", "O"], [":", "O"], ["0088-02-7912540", "O"], ["", "O"], ["00977-1-44-26-269", "O"], [":", "O"], ["HEDAYETUL.SAMES", "O"], ["@", "O"], ["YAHOO.COM", "O"], [":", "O"], ["Hedayetul", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Islam", "ORGANIZATION"], [":", "O"], ["CEO", "O"], ["Address", "O"], ["Phone", "O"], ["Fax", "O"], ["Email", "O"], ["Contact", "O"], ["Person", "O"], ["Designation", "O"], ["Firm", "O"], ["Name", "O"], ["Address", "O"], ["Phone", "O"], ["Fax", "O"], ["Email", "O"], ["Contact", "O"], ["Person", "O"], ["Designation", "O"], ["Closing", "O"], ["date", "O"], ["for", "O"], ["submission", "O"], ["of", "O"], ["proposals", "O"], ["is", "O"], ["on", "O"], ["19", "O"], ["March", "O"], ["2015", "O"], [".", "O"]]}